Guide to the 2000 Voting Technology Archive.
Voting Technology Archive, 2000
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
2000 Voting Technology Archive, 2000-2004.
6615
Cornell University.Dept. of Science & Technology Studies.
17 cubic feet.
Audio Recordings, Correspondence, Newspapers, Printed Materials, Publications, Reports.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection documents the technological aspects of the contested presidential vote in 2000.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Funded through the National Science Foundation, the archive is the result of a collaborative project between the Cornell Department of Science and Technology Studies at Cornell and the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The collection documents the technological aspects of the contested presidential vote in 2000, with special emphasis on the Florida recount. It includes documents, interviews, news clippings, articles, books, audio and video recordings, and artifacts donated by major government and research institutions, as well as media sources that played a significant role in the reporting of the election. Among the artifacts is a Palm Beach voting machine, used in the 2000 election, complete with the infamous butterfly ballot and hanging chads. The collection also includes a series pertaining to e-voting and the 2004 election.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University; Harvard University; John F. Kennedy School of Government.
Titles:
Palm Beach Post
Subjects:
Presidents--United States--Election--2000.; Presidents--United States--Election--2004.; Voting--Technological innovations--United States.; Press and politics--United States
Places:
Florida; United States--Politics and government--1993-2001; United States--Politics and government--2001-
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I: 2000 Election Material
Boxes 8, 10
Subseries A: Florida County Recounts
Boxes 1-8
Subseries B: Leon County Court Case
Box 9
Subseries C: Examples of Official General Election Ballots, Florida
Box 25
Subseries D: Election Results
Box 21
Series II: E-voting and the 2004 Election
Boxes 11, 12
Series III: Voting Technology Reference Material
Box 12
Series IV: Roy G. Saltman Papers on Election Policy and Technology
Box 12
Series V: Palm Beach Post Clippings
Boxes 13-18
Series VI: Mark Seibel's Notes and Files
Box 21
Series VII: Audio Visual Material
Boxes 19, 20
Series VIII: Book Publications
Box 26
Series IX: Voting Technology Exhibit Items, October 28, 2004
Boxes 22, 23
Series X: Voting Technology Ephemera
Box 24
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I: 2000 Election Material
  - Avante Vote-Trakker and Recount Reports, December 2000 - April 2001 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Mark Seibel's Planning File With Maps (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Escambia County - Hand Recount of Machine-counted Blank Ballots (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Faxes - Media Evaluation & Invoice, December 2000 - March 2001 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - State of Florida Precince Reporting of Undervotes for Optical Scan and Manually-counted Counties, December 2000 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Tapping New Data Territory Workshop, December 2001 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Overvotes, November 2000 - April 2001 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - State of Florida Reporting of Undervotes for Punch Card Counties (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Absentee Ballots, November 2000 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Indian River County Summary (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - The New Jargon, December 1, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Wrapping Up the Election, December 1, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - URL's on the 2000 Presidential Election, June 7, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Report of the National Workshop on Internet Voting (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Electronic Voting, March 23, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - A Preliminary Assessment, February 1, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Statement on Electronic Voting, January 1, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Generic Security Assessment, January 1, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Voting Automation, November 1, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - System Integrity Revisited, January 1, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Voting and Technology, December 15, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - No Voting Machine Is Going To Be Perfect, November 30, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - The Importance of Recounting Votes, November 13, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Public Statement Presented at the National Press Club, January 18, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Disenfranchised by Design, January 1, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Letter to Governor Bush, March 8, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Collection of Protest Chants and Songs, January 1, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - 13 Myths About the Results of the 2000 Election, November 27, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - 13 Myths About the Results of the 2000 Election, November 13, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - 13 Myths About the Election Results of the 2000 Election, November 14, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Official Florida Presidential Ballot, November 15, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Touchdown, November 28, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Hail to the Thief v.1.0, July 30, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Bill Press: More Evidence Bush Stole the Election, July 23, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Florida Congressman Demands Answers, July 20, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Dirty Pool in Florida, July 17, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Series-Skipper TM: There's A Scandal in There Somewhere!, July 17, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Election 2000: The Race Tightens Up!, January 28, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - The Federal Regulation of Elections, June 29, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - To Assure Pride and Confidence in the Electoral Process, August 1, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - What Counts as a Vote?, June 29, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Senate Government Reform Testimony, May 9, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - House Administration Testimony, May 10, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - General Overview for Getting a Voting System Qualified (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Voting Systems That are NASED Qualified (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Examining Internet Voting in Washington (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - A Report on the Feasibility of Internet Voting, January 1, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Security Considerations for Remote Electronic Voting Over the Internet, January 2000 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Accuracy, Integrity, and Security in Computerized Vote Tallying, August 1, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Adopting Computerized Voting in Developing Countries, January 1, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Electronic Voting Hot List, January 19, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Voting After Florida: No Easy Answers, March 19, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Electronic Voting, January 1, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - The Modern Democratic Revolution, January 1, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Getting the Chad Out, January 1, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Palm Beach County Wiped Out Computer Files, August 1, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Fla. Ballot Files May Be Gone, August 1, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Katherine Harris' Office Resisting Florida Election Reforms, August 4, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Florida's Flawed "Voter-cleansing" Program, December 4, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Democracy Hypochondria, August 2, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - The Web Reaches Into Palm Beach County, November 10, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - U.S. Supreme Court Ruling on 2000 Election Was Correct, August 8, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - The Governor's Select Task Force on Election Procedures, February 1, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - William D. Delahunt vs. Philip W. Johnston & Others - Decision, October - November 1996 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - The NYS-ECA Reporter Vol. 10, Issue 1, January 2002 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Report and Recommendation to the Marion County Election Board, February 24, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 2000 Florida Registration and Votiong Guide, July 27, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Setting the Standard for Election Integrity, January 16, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - ChoicePlus Brochure, January 2000 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Statistical Report, November 2, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - the History of Voting Machines, January 2000 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Chad Painting, January 2000 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Full Text of Proposed Olympia Teledemocracy Ordinances, January 2000 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - First Fifty-State Survey of Election Irregularities, August 20, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - How To Make Over One Million Votes Disappear: Electoral Sleight of Hand in the 2000 Presidential Election, August 20, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Florida Legislative Secretly Authorized A New Felons Purge, August 21, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Florida Voting Reforms face Discrimination Review, August 20, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Florida Voting Reform Discriminate Lawsuit Says, August 15, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - New York Times, Washington Post Suppress Media Recount of Florida Vote, September 25, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Residual Votes Attributable to Technology, March 30, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Assorted Comments on the Election Controversy, November 1, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gore's Concession Speech, December 13, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Bush's Acceptance Speech, December 13, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Deadline for Certification on County Results, November 13, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Definitions of Error in Vote Tabulation, November 13, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Manual Recount Procedure, November 13, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Manual Recount Procedures and Partial Certification, November 13, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Media Cover Up of Gore Victory, October 31, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Comments from John Ahmann (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Doug Jones' Collection of Punch Card Ballots (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Voting Technologies (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Income and Racial Disparities in the Undercount in the 2000 Election, July 9, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Election Reform in Detroit..., April 5, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Invalidated Ballots in the 1996 Presidential Election, May 1, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Report on the National Workshop on Internet Voting, March 1, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Effective Use of Computing Technology in Vote Tallying, January 1, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Computer Assisted Vote Tallying An Overview of the Problems..., March 25, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - California Internet Voting Task Force Report, January 1, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - The Modern Democratic Revolution: An Objective Survey, January 1, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Analysis of Internet Voting Proposals (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Electronic(Mechanical) Vote Tabulation: Part Two Why Some People Do Not Vote, January 1, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - CFP '93- Assuming Accuracy Integrity and Security in National Elections, February 12, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Adopting Computerized Voting in Developing Countries, January 1, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Missouri Voter Registration and Casting Ballot Part One, January 1, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2700 McDermott v. Harris, November 12-28, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2700 McDermott v. Harris, November 12-28, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2700 McDermott v. Harris, November 12-28, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Leon County Court Case No. 00-2700 McDermott v. Harris, November 12-28, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Improving the Procurement Process National Computerized Election System by Jay Cornish, Unisys (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Election Procurement: Open and Free by Stephen Connolly and Bruce Hatch (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Taylor v. Martin Country Canvas Bd. (CV-00-2850, SC00-2448), December 1-12, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Taylor v. Martin Canvas Bd. (CV-00-2850, SC00-2448), December 1-12, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Taylor v. Martin Canvas Bd. (CV-00-2850, SC00-2448), December 1-12, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Taylor v. Martin Canvas Bd. (CV-00-2850, SC00-2448), December 1-12, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Taylor v. Martin Canvas Bd. (CV-00-2850, SC00-2448), December 1-12, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Taylor v. Martin Canvas Bd. (CV-00-2850, SC00-2448), December 1-12, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - "The Use of Pre-scored Punch Card Ballots Should Be Ended", August 29, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Filling the Institutional Void in Election Administration, September 10, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Florida Democratic Elected Official Steals Ballot Punching Machine, November 16, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Election Reform: An Analysis of Proposals and the Commission's Recommendations for Improving America's Election System, June 18, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - United States District Court Southern District of Florida Case No. 01-CIV-120-GOLD, July 24, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - EZ Access Voter Registration and Tracking, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Ballot Printing System II Overview (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - "Gatekeepers to the Franchise: Election Administrationand Voter Participation in New York" (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Did the Media's Early Call of Florida for Gore Change the Election, November 15, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Likelihood of Altering the Outcome of the Florida 2000 Presidential Election by Recount, January 5, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Observing the 1999 Public Consulatation Process in East Timor, June 2000 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - AAPOR Did Not Intend to Criticize NBC and MSNBC for their overall use of a group of undecided voters, October 20, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - The National Commission on Federal Election Reform Report, July 31, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - The Voter Rights March: Chants, Songs, and Poems (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Urbam Legend Claim: The Word 'Chad', November 20, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Fladell v. Palm Beach (CL 00-10965), November 8-27, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Fl. Dem. Party v. Broward County Canvas Bd., November 14-20, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Nelson v. Robinson (Fla. Dist. Ct. App), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Accuracy, Integrity, and Security in Computerized Vote Tallying, August 1, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - The Importance of Research and Standards in Effective Election Administration, May 22, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - CRS Report for Congress: Election Reform: Overview and Issues, November 30, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Voter Registration Application, July 25, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Federalism and the Crisis in Election Administration, October 27, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Conducting Elections in Maryland Considerations for the future, January 4, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Felon Database (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - State of Florida Reporting of Undervotes (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - A Look Ahead: Election Timeline, November 12, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - George W. Bush Et. Al., Petitioners v. Albert Gore Jr., Et. Al., December 12, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Recount 'Em All, or None at All, November 12, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Subseries A: Florida County Recounts
    - Alachua County - Beverly Hill, December 2000 - January 2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alachua County - Ballot Review (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Baker County - John Barton, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Baker County - Ballot Review (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bay County - Melanie Williams-Boyd, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bay County - Ballot Review (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bradford County - Terry L. Vaughn, December 2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bradford County - Ballot Review (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Brevard County - Fred D. Galey, December 2000 - February 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Brevard County - Ballot Review (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Broward County, Florida General Election Canvass Reports (Over & under) (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Broward County, Florida General Election Canvass Reports (Over & under) (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Broward County, Florida General Election Canvass Reports (Over & under) - Recount (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Broward County - Jane Carroll, December 2000 - April 2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 2 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 3 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 4 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 5 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 6 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 7 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 8 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 9 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 10 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 11 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 12 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 13 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 14 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 15 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 16 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 17 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 18 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 19 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 20 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 21 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 22 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 23 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 24 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 25 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 26 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 27 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 28 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 29 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 30 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 31 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 32 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 33 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 34 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 35 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 36-40 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 41-49 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 50 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 51 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 52 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 53 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 54 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 55 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 56 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 57 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 58 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 59 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 60 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 61 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 62 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 63 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 64 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 65 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 66-67 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 68 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 69-70 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 71 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 72 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 73 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 75 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 78 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct 79 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 01-4 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 6-8 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 10-15 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 16-18 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 21-25 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 26-29 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 31-35 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 36-40 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 41-44 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 46-49 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 51-55 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 56-60 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 61-65 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 66-70 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 73-74 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 76-79 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 81-84 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Precinct AB 87-88 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other Absetee Ballots and Advance Ballots (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Broward County - Ballot Review, Other (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Broward County - Recount Precinct by Precinct (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Broward County - Recount Precinct by Precinct (Box 3, Folder 11)